<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<refworks xmlns:refworks="www.refworks.com/xml/">


<reference>
<id>501</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Lorig, T.S.</a1>
<t1>Introduction</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>International Journal of Psychophysiology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>36</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>89</sp>
<op>90</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab></ab>
<sn>01678760</sn>
<do>10.1016/S0167-8760(99)00103-8</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Editorial</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>502</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Lorig, T.S.</a1>
<t1>The application of electroencephalographic techniques to the study of human olfaction: A review and tutorial</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>International Journal of Psychophysiology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>36</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>91</sp>
<op>104</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>The use of a variety of electrophysiological techniques to</ab>
<sn>01678760</sn>
<do>10.1016/S0167-8760(99)00104-X</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>503</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Degener, A.</a1>
<a1>Lubin, T.</a1>
<t1>The pahlavi translation technique as illustrated</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>Indo-Iranian Journal</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>43</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>403</sp>
<op>406</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab></ab>
<sn>00197246</sn>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>504</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>McDaniel</a1>
<t1>Field notes:   reflections of anglers and hunters</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>GN1 .J374 v.3</cn>
<u4>b1535401~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>505</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>McDaniel</a1>
<t1>Archaeological investigations at the Paxton House (Glen Maury) in Buena Vista, Virginia</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>F234.B94 S78 2000</cn>
<u4>b1562812~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>506</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Miller</a1>
<t1>Crusoe's Island:   the story of a writer and a place</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>1928556043 (acid-free paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PS3563.I38 Z465 2000</cn>
<u4>b1523906~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>507</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Miller</a1>
<t1>This is where we live:   short stories by 25 contemporary North Carolina writers</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0807825832 (cloth : alk. paper);0807848956 (pbk. : ak. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PS558.N8 T48 2000</cn>
<u4>b1536219~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>508</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Morel</a1>
<t1>Lincoln's sacred effort:   defining religion's role in American self-government</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0739101056 (cloth : alk. paper);0739101064 (paper : alk. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>E457.2 .M85 2000</cn>
<u4>b1517362~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>509</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Cravens, K.S.</a1>
<a1>Oliver, E.G.</a1>
<t1>The influence of culture on pension plans</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>International Journal of Accounting</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>35</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>521</sp>
<op>537</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>It is widely recognized that culture is a dimension affecting a vast array of management and social choices. However, we know little about the effect of culture on choices that combine both business and social issues in an accounting setting. E</ab>
<sn>10944060</sn>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Article</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>510</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Peterson</a1>
<t1>Corpo del papa. English;The Pope's body"</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0226034372 (hardcover : alk. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>bX1069.5 .P3713 2000</cn>
<u4>b1527965~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>511</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Radulescu</a1>
<t1>Nature, woman, and the art of politics</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0847692469 (cloth : alk. paper);0847692477 (paper : alk. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PN56.5.W64 N37 2000</cn>
<u4>b1530955~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>512</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Reese</a1>
<t1>University physics</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0534246559;053439650x (suppl.)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>FACULTY PUBLICATIONS</cn>
<u4>b1491461~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>513</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Reese</a1>
<t1>Student solutions manual for Reese's University physics</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0534352340 (v. 1 : pbk.);0534370217 (v. 2. : pbk.);9780534352349</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>FACULTY PUBLICATIONS</cn>
<u4>b1671674~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>514</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Reese</a1>
<t1>Complete solutions manual for University physics</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0534369049 (v. 2 : pbk.)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>FACULTY PUBLICATIONS</cn>
<u4>b1671675~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>515</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Rush</a1>
<t1>Does redistricting make a difference?:   partisan representation and electoral behavior</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp></sp>
<op></op>
<sn>0739101927 (pbk. : alk. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>JK1341 .R87 2000</cn>
<u4>b1535319~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>516</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Rush, M.E.</a1>
<t1>Redistricting and partisan fluidity: Do we really know a gerrymander when we see one?</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>Political Geography</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>19</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>249</sp>
<op>260</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>Redistricting analysis and the concept of gerrymander</ab>
<sn>09626298</sn>
<do>10.1016/S0962-6298(99)00048-7</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Article</u3>
<cn>Â </cn>
<u4>Â </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>517</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Simurda, M.C.</a1>
<a1>Knox, J.S.</a1>
<t1>ITS sequence evidence for the disjunct distribution between Virginia and Missouri of the narrow endemic Helenium virginicum (Asteraceae)</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>Journal of the Torrey Botanical Society</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>127</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>316</sp>
<op>323</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>Simurda, M. C. and J. S. Knox (Department of Biology, Washington and Lee University, Lexington, VA 24450-0303). ITS sequence evidence for the disj</ab>
<sn>10955674</sn>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Article</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>518</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Smith, R.T.</a1>
<t1>But with blood</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp></sp>
<op></op>
<sn></sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PS3569.M537914 B85 2000</cn>
<u4>b1535427~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>519</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Smith, R.T.</a1>
<t1>Lilting:   poems</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp></sp>
<op></op>
<sn></sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PS3569.M537914 L55 2000</cn>
<u4>b1535428~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>520</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Spencer</a1>
<t1>Geologic maps:   a practical guide to the preparation and interpretation of geologic maps:   for geologists, geographers, engineers, and planners</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>130115835</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>QE36 .S64 2000</cn>
<u4>b1522520~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>521</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Strong</a1>
<t1>Working in the world:   Jimmy Carter and the making of American foreign policy</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0807124451 (cl. : alk. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>E872 .S79 2000</cn>
<u4>b1516500~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>522</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Stuart</a1>
<t1>The fictional world of William Hoffman</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0826212751 (alk. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PS3558.O34638 Z66 2000</cn>
<u4>b1523652~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>523</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Sukow, D.W.</a1>
<a1>Gauthier, D.J.</a1>
<t1>Entraining power-dropout events in an external-cavity semiconductor laser using weak modulation of the injection current</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>IEEE Journal of Quantum Electronics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>36</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>175</sp>
<op>183</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>We measure experimentally the effects of injection current modulation on the statistical distribution </ab>
<sn>00189197</sn>
<do>10.1109/3.823463</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Article</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>524</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Rogister, F.</a1>
<a1>Sukow, D.W.</a1>
<a1>Gavrielides, A.</a1>
<a1>Megret, P.</a1>
<a1>Deparis, O.</a1>
<a1>Blondel, M.</a1>
<t1>Experimental demonstration of suppression of low-frequency fluctuations and stabilization of an external-cavity laser diode</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>Optics Letters</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>25</vo>
<is>11</is>
<sp>808</sp>
<op>810</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>We de</ab>
<sn>01469592</sn>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Article</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>525</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Hitlin, C.</a1>
<a1>Roy, C.</a1>
<a1>Tallman, D.</a1>
<t1>eDesk Online - Internal development and deployment of Help Desk management software</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>Proceedings ACM SIGUCCS User Services Conference</jf>
<t2></t2>
<sp>339</sp>
<op>340</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>After four years of operation, the University Computing HelpDesk at Washington and Lee University, previously student-run and student-centered, needed to become more reliable and to serve a wider audience. The HelpDesk has about</ab>
<rt>Conference Proceedings</rt>
<u3>Conference Proceedings</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>526</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Valachovic, L.R.</a1>
<a1>Tuchler, M.F.</a1>
<a1>Dulligan, M.</a1>
<a1>Droz-Georget, Th.</a1>
<a1>Zyrianov, M.</a1>
<a1>Kolessov, A.</a1>
<a1>Reisler, H.</a1>
<a1>Wittig, C.</a1>
<t1>Photoinitiated H2CO unimolecular decomposition: Accessing H+HCO products via S0 and T1 pathways</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf>Journal of Chemical Physics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>112</vo>
<is>6</is>
<sp>2752</sp>
<op>2761</op>
<lk></lk>
<ab>The photoinitiated unimolecular decomposition of formaldehyde via the H+HCO radical channel has been examined at energies where the S0</ab>
<sn>00219606</sn>
<do>10.1063/1.480849</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Article</u3>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>527</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Velasquez</a1>
<t1>Nature, woman, and the art of politics</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<t2></t2>
<sn>0847692469 (cloth : alk. paper);0847692477 (paper : alk. paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PN56.5.W64 N37 2000</cn>
<u4>b1530955~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>528</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Warren</a1>
<t1>Reading under the sign of nature:   new essays in ecocriticism</t1>
<yr>2000</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp></sp>
<op></op>
<sn>0874806488 (pbk. : acid-free paper)</sn>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PS163 .R4 2000</cn>
<u4>b1622496~S0</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>726</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Abah, A. L.</a1>
<t1>Popular culture and social change in Africa: The case of the Nigerian video industry</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Media, Culture & Society</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>31</vo>
<is>5</is>
<sp>731</sp>
<op>748</op>
<ab>The emerging video-film pop culture in Nigeria is examined for its potential to stimulate social change in the society. Three video-films from the industry were analysed for social commentary and options for change in the society. The study concludes that the industry has a potential to stimulate social change in the society, but its commercial nature and its melodramatic content may create impediments. © 2009 SAGE Publications.</ab>
<sn>ISSN (printed): 0163-4437. ISSN (electronic): 1460-3675</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>727</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Aleman,A.;Feldman,N. S.;Ross,W. T.</a1>
<t1>The hardy space of a slit domain</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Frontiers in Mathematics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>2009</vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>1</sp>
<op>143</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>16608046</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>728</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Alty,Lisa T.</a1>
<t1>Analysis of fatty acid methyl esters in egg yolk using GC-MS</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Journal of chemical education</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>86</vo>
<is>8</is>
<sp>962</sp>
<op>965</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>0021-9584</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>730</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Bailey,C. F. -P</a1>
<t1>A new Iracema: The voice of the native woman in the work of Eliane Potiguara</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Revista Iberoamericana</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>76</vo>
<is>230</is>
<sp>201</sp>
<op>215</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>00349631</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>731</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Bailey,Matthew</a1>
<t1>The poetics of speech in the medieval Spanish epic</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>147</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9781442641563</a1>
<a1>1442641568</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>PQ6088.B35 2010</cn>
<u4>b1743420</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>732</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Bell,M. C.</a1>
<t1>Valuing all families</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Law, Culture and the Humanities</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>5</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>288</sp>
<op>316</op>
<ab>Anti-gay marriage amendments proliferate, and current welfare legislation includes coercive marriage promotion programs. This article argues that government sponsorship and promotion of the traditional institution of heterosexual marriage-based family are antithetical to the liberal democratic values that most Americans would claim are foundational principles of their society: liberty and individuality. I suggest that, in order to make the social and legal institution of family consistent with professed public values, it should be transformed from the traditional structure into a new structure that is (1) flexible and customizable, and (2) eligible for direct public support for its role in social reproduction. © 2009 Association for the Study of Law, Culture and the Humanities.</ab>
<sn>17438721</sn>
<do>10.1177/1743872109102493</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>733</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Benefiel,Rebecca R.</a1>
<t1>Dialogues of ancient graffiti in the house of Maius Castricius in Pompeii</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>American Journal of Archaeology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>114</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp>59</sp>
<op>101</op>
<ab>Ancient graffiti have traditionally been studied as brief texts, but that is only part of the information they communicate. I propose a more comprehensive approach that considers their content and form and situates them more firmly within their physical and social environment. Engaging more closely with the spatial context of graffiti informs us about the ancient use of space and the human activity within it. It also allows us to see what else, besides text, was inscribed on the walls of Pompeii. The concept of the dialogue offers a flexible model of inquiry and provides a fresh perspective for examining the numerous graffiti of a residential space. From number games to drawings to clever compositions of poetry, the graffiti of the House of Maius Castricius reveal wide participation and a strong interest in the act of writing, a popular activity here and throughout Pompeii.</ab>
<sn>00029114</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>734</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Bourdon,Paul S.</a1>
<t1>Bellwethers for boundedness of composition operators on weighted banach spaces of analytic functions</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Journal of the Australian Mathematical Society</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>86</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>305</sp>
<op>314</op>
<ab>Let be the open unit disc, let v:(0,) be a typical weight, and let Hv be the corresponding weighted Banach space consisting of analytic functions f on such that $\|f\|-v:=\sup -{z\in \mathbb {D}}v(z)\lvert f(z)\rvert \less \infty $. We call Hv a typical-growth space. For a holomorphic self-map of , let C denote the composition operator induced by . We say that C is a bellwether for boundedness of composition operators on typical-growth spaces if for each typical weight v, C acts boundedly on Hv only if all composition operators act boundedly on Hv. We show that a sufficient condition for C to be a bellwether for boundedness is that have an angular derivative of modulus less than 1 at a point on . We raise the question of whether this angular-derivative condition is also necessary for C to be a bellwether for boundedness. © 2009 Copyright Australian Mathematical Society.</ab>
<sn>1446-7887</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>735</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Bourdon,P. S.;Gerjuoy,E.</a1>
<t1>Overcoming a limitation of deterministic dense coding with a nonmaximally entangled initial state</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Physical Review A - Atomic, Molecular, and Optical Physics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>81</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp> </sp>
<op> </op>
<ab>Under two-party deterministic dense coding, Alice communicates (perfectly distinguishable) messages to Bob via a qudit from a pair of entangled qudits in pure state |Ψ. If |Ψ represents a maximally entangled state (i.e., each of its Schmidt coefficients is 1/d), then Alice can convey to Bob one of d2 distinct messages. If |Ψ is not maximally entangled, then Ji [Phys. Rev. A 73, 034307 (2006)] have shown that under the original deterministic dense-coding protocol, in which messages are encoded by unitary operations performed on Alice's qudit, it is impossible to encode d2-1 messages. Encoding d2-2 messages is possible</a1>
<a1>see, for example, the numerical studies by Mozes [Phys. Rev. A 71, 012311 (2005)]. Answering a question raised by Wu [Phys. Rev. A 73, 042311 (2006)], we show that when |Ψ is not maximally entangled, the communications limit of d2-2 messages persists even when the requirement that Alice encode by unitary operations on her qudit is weakened to allow encoding by more general quantum operators. We then describe a dense-coding protocol that can overcome this limitation with high probability, assuming the largest Schmidt coefficient of |Ψ is sufficiently close to 1/d. In this protocol, d2-2 of the messages are encoded via unitary operations on Alice's qudit, and the final (d2-1)-th message is encoded via a non-trace-preserving quantum operation. © 2010 The American Physical Society.</ab>
<sn>10502947</sn>
<do>10.1103/PhysRevA.81.022314</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>736</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Bourdon,P. S.;Narayan,S. K.</a1>
<t1>Normal weighted composition operators on the Hardy space H2 (U)</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Journal of Mathematical Analysis and Applications</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>367</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp>278</sp>
<op>286</op>
<ab>Let φ be an analytic function on the open unit disc U such that φ (U) ⊆ U, and let ψ be an analytic function on U such that the weighted composition operator Wψ, φ defined by Wψ, φ f = ψ f ○ φ is bounded on the Hardy space H2 (U). We characterize those weighted composition operators on H2 (U) that are unitary, showing that in contrast to the unweighted case (ψ ≡ 1), every automorphism of U induces a unitary weighted composition operator. A conjugation argument, using these unitary operators, allows us to describe all normal weighted composition operators on H2 (U) for which the inducing map φ fixes a point in U. This description shows both ψ and φ must be linear fractional in order for Wψ, φ to be normal (assuming φ fixes a point in U). In general, we show that if Wψ, φ is normal on H2 (U) and ψ ≢ 0, then φ must be either univalent on U or constant. Descriptions of spectra are provided for the operator Wψ, φ : H2 (U) → H2 (U) when it is unitary or when it is normal and φ fixes a point in U. © 2010 Elsevier Inc. All rights reserved.</ab>
<sn>0022247X</sn>
<do>10.1016/j.jmaa.2010.01.006</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>737</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Bower,A. B.;Grau,L. S.</a1>
<t1>Explicit donations and inferred endorsements: Do corporate social responsibility initiatives suggest a nonprofi t organization endorsement?</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Journal of Advertising</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>38</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>113</sp>
<op>126</op>
<ab>Corporate social responsibility (CSR) initiatives, while not necessarily intended to constitute an endorsement of the brand by the participating nonprofit organization, may nonetheless be perceived by consumers as such. Our experimental findings of two common types of CSR initiatives (licensing associations and cause-related marketing) suggest that not only can the method of presentation of CSR initiatives in advertising result in perceptions of nonprofit endorsement, but also may be entirely confused with explicit seals of approval. Heightened processing motivation either fails to correct the misperception of nonprofit endorsement or may even enhance its perception as a result of the presentation of the CSR initiative in an advertisement. Level of fit between the nonprofit and for-profit brand may also result in increased perception of endorsement. Given the positive effects of third-party endorsements, our results suggest that some CSR initiatives may result in consumer inferences that are inaccurate but desirable for the company, even while these inferences have potentially negative consequences for the nonprofit. © 2009 American Academy of Advertising. All rights reserved.</ab>
<sn>00913367</sn>
<do>10.2753/JOA0091-3367380308</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>738</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Braunschneider,Theresa</a1>
<t1>Our coquettes :capacious desire in the eighteenth century</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>189</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780813928098</a1>
<a1>0813928095</a1>
<a1>9780813928142</a1>
<a1>0813928141</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>PR448.F55B73 2009</cn>
<u4>b1718109</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>739</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Brodie,Laura Fairchild</a1>
<t1>Love in a time of homeschooling: a mother and daughter's uncommon year</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>263</sp>
<op></op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780061706462</a1>
<a1>0061706469</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>LC40.B76 2010</cn>
<u4>b1729088</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>740</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Brodie,Laura Fairchild</a1>
<t1>The widow's season</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>308</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780425227657</a1>
<a1>0425227650</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>PS3602.R63486W53 2009</cn>
<u4>b1707438</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>741</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Campbell,Julie A.</a1>
<t1>The horse in Virginia :an illustrated history</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>296</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780813928166</a1>
<a1>0813928168</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>SF284.U5C18 2010</cn>
<u4>b1734626</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>742</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Carey,M.</a1>
<t1>Latin american environmental history: Current trends, interdisciplinary insights, and future directions</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Environmental History</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>14</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>221</sp>
<op>252</op>
<ab>Latin American environmental history has traditionally focused on three categories of research: colonialism, capitalism, and conservation. It has also emphasized tragic tales of resource extraction and environmental destruction, primarily at the hands of imperial powers. Though important issues, these stories of degradation and exploitation also constrain the historiography. To broaden the field and push its theoretical grounding in new directions, this essay analyzes environmental history research conducted by non- historians. It highlights scholarship in several areas, including the history of natural sciences, cultural landscapes, environmental narratives, nature consumption, disasters, and social history. More dialogue across scholarly disciplines can help historians of Latin America reconceptualize the meaning of nature, blur nature-culture boundaries, and integrate environmental history with the region's broader historiography.</ab>
<sn>10845453</sn>
<do>10.1093/envhis/14.2.221</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>743</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Carey,Mark</a1>
<t1>In the shadow of melting glaciers: climate change and Andean society</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>273</sp>
<op></op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780195396065</a1>
<a1>0195396065</a1>
<a1>9780195396072</a1>
<a1>0195396073</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>QC988.P4C37 2010</cn>
<u4>b1739535</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>744</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Carson,T. M.;Bradley,S. Q.;Fekete,B. L.;Millard,J. T.;LaRiviere,F. J.</a1>
<t1>Forensic analysis of canine DNA samples in the undergraduate biochemistry laboratory</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Journal of chemical education</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>86</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>376</sp>
<op>378</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>00219584</sn>
<do>10.1021/ed086p376</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>745</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Casey,J. F.;Brown,C.;Schuhmann,P.</a1>
<t1>Are tourists willing to pay additional fees to protect corals in Mexico?</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Journal of Sustainable Tourism</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>18</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>557</sp>
<op>573</op>
<ab>This paper seeks to determine if tourists visiting the Riviera Maya, Mexico, are willing to pay an entrance fee to enhance coral reef protection</a1>
<a1>and if so, how much would they pay? A discrete choice contingent valuation experiment with almost 400 visitors was used to determine a measure of compensating variation for contributing to a public trust to protect corals. Results suggest that there are significant possibilities for implementing a coral fund to raise revenues for coral protection programs in the Riviera Maya region of Mexico's Yucatan Peninsula. We estimate a mean willingness to pay (WTP) of over $55.00. Additionally, all three estimation methods used produced relatively similar values for mean WTP, ranging from $42 to $58. With approximately five million visitors passing through the Cancun International Airport each year, this suggests that it may be possible to collect between $100 and $400 million annually for coral reef management programs. Thinking very conservatively, if we take a $20 fee and assume that only 50% of tourists would actually be willing to pay, that is still $50 million left on the table annually. © 2010 Taylor & Francis.</ab>
<sn>09669582</sn>
<do>10.1080/09669580903513079</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>746</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Caviglia-Harris,J. L.;Chambers,D.;Kahn,J. R.</a1>
<t1>Taking the U out of Kuznets. A comprehensive analysis of the EKC and environmental degradation</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Ecological Economics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>68</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>1149</sp>
<op>1159</op>
<ab>Unlike most Environmental Kuznets Curve (EKC) studies which focus on narrow measures of pollution as proxies for environmental quality, we test the validity of the EKC using the Ecological Footprint (EF), a more comprehensive measure of environmental degradation. We find no empirical evidence of an EKC relationship between the EF and economic development, and only limited support for such a relationship among the components of the EF. In addition, we discover that energy is largely responsible for the lack of an EKC relationship, and that energy consumption levels would have to be cut by over 50% in order for a statistically significant EKC relationship to emerge from the data. Overall, these results suggest that growth alone will not lead to sustainable development. © 2008 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</ab>
<sn>09218009</sn>
<do>10.1016/j.ecolecon.2008.08.006</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>747</id>
<u1>0</u1>
U2 2012/01/06
<a1>Touve,D.</a1>
<a1>Chen,Y.;</a1>
<t1>Conformity, political participation, and economic rewards: The case of Chinese private entrepreneurs</t1>
<yr>2011</yr>
<jf>Asia Pacific Journal of Management</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>28</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>529</sp>
<op>553</op>
<ab>Using institutional and resource dependence theories as the conceptual framework, this study identifies three forms of conformity-political, economic, and social-that can affect the level of private entrepreneurs' formal political participation in a transition economy. Data from a 2004 national-wide survey of 3,012 private firms in China show that political conformity (indicated by membership in the ruling party), economic conformity (amount of taxes paid), and social conformity (amount of charity donated) are each antecedents to private entrepreneurs' formal political participation. Moreover, political conformity negatively moderates the relationship between social conformity and private entrepreneurs' formal political participation-for party members, a lesser amount of charity is associated with higher levels of political position as compared to non-party members. We also found that the rewards of formal political participation have institutional boundaries: political participation can indeed bring private entrepreneurs economic rewards such as a greater amount of loans from state banks but not from shareholding and underground banks. © 2009 Springer Science+Business Media, LLC.</ab>
<sn>02174561</a1>
<a1>ESSN: 1572-9958</sn>
<do>10.1007/s10490-009-9171-2</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>748</id>
<u1>0</u1>
U2 2011-08-29
<a1>Connelly,William F.</a1>
<t1>James Madison rules America: the constitutional origins of congressional partisanship</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>339</sp>
<op></op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780742599659</a1>
<a1>0742599655</a1>
<a1>9780742599673</a1>
<a1>0742599671</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>KF4930.C66 2010</cn>
<u4>b1743475</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>749</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Costello,M. C.;Madden,D. J.;Mitroff,S. R.;Whiting,W. L.</a1>
<t1>Age-related decline of visual processing components in change detection</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Psychology and aging</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>25</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>356</sp>
<op>368</op>
<ab>Previous research has suggested that an age-related decline in change detection may be due to older adults using a more conservative response criterion. However, this finding may reflect methodological limitations of the traditional change detection design, in which displays are presented continuously until a change is detected. Across 2 experiments, the authors assessed adult age differences in a version of change detection that required a response after each pair of pre- and postchange displays, thus reducing the potential contribution of response criterion. Older adults performed worse than younger adults, committing more errors and requiring a greater number of display cycles for correct detection. These age-related performance declines were substantially reduced after controlling statistically for elementary perceptual speed. Search strategy was largely similar for the 2 age groups, but perceptual speed was less successful in accounting for age-related variance in detectability when a more precise spatial localization of change was required (Experiment 2). Thus, the negative effect of aging in the present tasks lies in a reduction of detection efficiency due largely to processing speed, though some strategy-level effects may also contribute. © 2010 American Psychological Association.</ab>
<sn>08827974</sn>
<do>10.1037/a0017625</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>750</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Craun,Edwin D.</a1>
<t1>Ethics and power in medieval English reformist writing</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>76</vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>217</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780521199322</a1>
<a1>0521199328</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>BR747.C73 2010</cn>
<u4>b1734607</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>751</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Cravens,K. S.;Oliver,E. G.;Stewart,J. S.</a1>
<t1>Can a positive approach to performance evaluation help accomplish your goals?</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Business horizons</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>53</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>269</sp>
<op>279</op>
<ab>Organizations typically depend upon performance evaluation measures to provide feedback to managers regarding the achievement of strategic objectives. However, performance evaluation is often focused on negative aspects of performance, suggesting that managers may not be receiving enough reinforcement of the positive elements of their decisions. When applied effectively, performance measures not only create desirable motivation, but also encourage communication and the exchange of information among managers. Under this scenario, individual managers achieve their personal goals, while the organization satisfies its strategic objectives. The application of positive organizational scholarship principles to performance evaluation metrics can help make the evaluation process more effective. Using performance measures framed in a positive manner can help generate more creativity, more problem-solving ability, and greater communication among managers, leading to progress toward organizational objectives. We illustrate this approach with the application of positive metrics to the balanced scorecard for mid-level managers in implementing business strategy. © 2009 Kelley School of Business, Indiana University.</ab>
<sn>00076813</sn>
<do>10.1016/j.bushor.2009.09.005</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>752</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Crotty,Kevin</a1>
<t1>The philosopher's song :the poets' influence on Plato</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>247</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780739144060</a1>
<a1>0739144065</a1>
<a1>9780739144084</a1>
<a1>0739144081</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>B398.P6C76 2009</cn>
<u4>b1731637</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>753</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Cumming,Douglas O.;Medill School of Journalism</a1>
<t1>The Southern press :literary legacies and the challenge of modernity</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>316</sp>
<op></op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780810123946</a1>
<a1>0810123940</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>PN4893.C78 2009</cn>
<u4>b1722198</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>754</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Cumming,Joseph B.</a1>
<t1>Bylines: writings from the American South, 1963-1997</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>247</sp>
<op></op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9781449023102</a1>
<a1>144902310X</a1>
<a1>9781449023096</a1>
<a1>1449023096</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book</u3>
<cn>PN4874.C887A25 2010</cn>
<u4>b1741377</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>755</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Darst,C. R.;Huffman,K. A.;Jarvis,J.</a1>
<t1>Conservation significance of America's Newest system of protected Areas: National Landscape Conservation system</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Natural Areas Journal</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>29</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>224</sp>
<op>254</op>
<ab>Using a dataset of special status animal species aggregated from NatureServe (2006), we assessed the conservation significance of the newest U.S. network of protected areas, the BLM-administered National Landscape Conservation System (NLCS) composed of ̃ 11 million hectares of specially designated conservation areas. We examined the number of special status animal species that occur within the NLCS as compared to the number that would be predicted by area alone, occurrences within the NLCS as compared to other BLM lands, and the conservation implications of these species-area relationships. Our analyses suggest that the NLCS plays a significant role in the conservation of special status species and the natural ecosystems on which they depend.</ab>
<sn>08858608</sn>
<do>10.3375/043.029.0304</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>756</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Davidson,T. L.;Chan,K.;Jarrard,L. E.;Kanoski,S. E.;Clegg,D. J.;Benoit,S. C.</a1>
<t1>Contributions of the hippocampus and medial prefrontal cortex to energy and body weight regulation</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Hippocampus</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>19</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>235</sp>
<op>252</op>
<ab>The effects of selective ibotenate lesions of the complete hippocampus (CHip), the hippocampal ventral pole (VP), or the medial prefrontal cortex (mPFC) in male rats were assessed on several measures related to energy regulation (i.e., body weight gain, food intake, body adiposity, metabolic activity, general behavioral activity, conditioned appetitive responding). The testing conditions were designed to minimize the nonspecific debilitating effects of these surgeries on intake and body weight. Rats with CHip and VP lesions exhibited significantly greater weight gain and food intake compared with controls. Furthermore, CHip-lesioned rats, but not rats with VP lesions, showed elevated metabolic activity, general activity in the dark phase of the light-dark cycle, and greater conditioned appetitive behavior, compared with control rats without these brain lesions. In contrast, rats with mPFC lesions were not different from controls on any of these measures. These results indicate that hippocampal damage interferes with energy and body weight regulation, perhaps by disrupting higher-order learning and memory processes that contribute to the control of appetitive and con-summatory behavior, © 2008 Wiley-Liss, Inc.</ab>
<sn>10509631</sn>
<do>10.1002/hipo.20499</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>757</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Davidson,T. L.;Kanoski,S. E.;Chan,K.;Clegg,D. J.;Benoit,S. C.;Jarrard,L. E.</a1>
<t1>Hippocampal Lesions Impair Retention of Discriminative Responding Based on Energy State Cues</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Behavioral neuroscience</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>124</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp>97</sp>
<op>105</op>
<ab>The present research investigated the hypothesis that the hippocampus is involved with the control of appetitive behavior by interoceptive hunger and satiety signals. Rats were trained to solve a food deprivation intensity discrimination problem in which stimuli produced by 0-hr and 24-hr food deprivation served as discriminative cues for the delivery of sucrose pellets. For Group 0+, sucrose pellets were delivered at the conclusion of each 4-min session that took place under 0-hr food deprivation, whereas no pellets were delivered during sessions that took place when the rats had been food deprived for 24 hr. Group 24+ received the reverse discriminative contingency (i.e., they received sucrose pellets under 24-hr but not under 0-hr food deprivation). When asymptotic discrimination performance was achieved (indexed by greater incidence of food magazine approach behavior on reinforced compared with nonreinforced sessions), half of the rats in each group received hippocampal lesions, and the remaining rats in each group were designated as sham- or nonlesioned controls. Following recovery from surgery, food deprivation discrimination performance was compared for lesioned and control rats in both Groups 0+ and 24+. Discriminative responding was impaired for rats with hippocampal lesions relative to their controls. This impairment was based largely on elevated responding to nonreinforced food deprivation cues. In addition, hippocampal damage was associated with increased body weight under conditions of ad libitum feeding. The results suggest that the inhibition of appetitive behavior by energy state signals may depend, in part, on the hippocampus. © 2010 American Psychological Association.</ab>
<sn>07357044</sn>
<do>10.1037/a0018402</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>758</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Diaz-Valenzuela,M. B.;Phillips,S. D.;France,M. B.;Gunn,M. E.;Clarke,M. L.</a1>
<t1>Enantioselective hydrogenation and transfer hydrogenation of bulky ketones catalysed by a ruthenium complex of a chiral tridentate ligand</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Chemistry - A European Journal</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>15</vo>
<is>5</is>
<sp>1227</sp>
<op>1232</op>
<ab>A study on the enantioselective hydrogenation of tertiary alkyl ketones catalysed by a novel class of tridentate-Ru complex is reported. In contrast to the extensively studied [RuCl2(diphos)(di-primary amine)] complexes, this new class of hydrogenation catalyst smoothly reduces these less reactive bulky ketones with up to 94% ee. The same catalyst system can also selectively reduce other potentially problematic substrates such as bulky heterocyclic ketones. Unusually for a pressure hydrogenation catalyst, similar enantioselectivity can be obtained under transfer hydrogenation conditions. The transfer hydrogenations are somewhat slower than the pressure hydrogenations, but this drawback is readily overcome, since we have discovered that a microwave accelerated transfer hydrogenation of the above ketones occurs within 20 min at about 90 °C with similar selectivity to that obtained in the pressure hydrogenation system. © 2009 Wiley-VCH Verlag GmbH & Co. KGaA.</ab>
<sn>09476539</sn>
<do>10.1002/chem.200801929</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>759</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Dickens,David Bruce</a1>
<t1>The pleasures of Franconia</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>434</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn> </sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>DD801.F565D53 2009</cn>
<u4>b1714926</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>760</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Dickovick,J. T.</a1>
<t1>Revolutionising local politics? Radical experiments in Burkina Faso, Ghana and Uganda in the 1980s</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Review of African Political Economy</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>36</vo>
<is>122</is>
<sp>519</sp>
<op>537</op>
<ab>This article compares three African countries whose attempts to transform local governance in the 1980s were among the most dramatic, particularly in rural areas: Burkina Faso under Thomas Sankara (1983-1987), Ghana in the early years of the Jerry Rawlings presidency (1981-1992), and Uganda under Yoweri Museveni (1985-present). Despite surface similarities, especially in the establishment of local 'people's defence councils' or 'resistance councils', the three experiments had quite different outcomes, as a function both of antecedent conditions in state-society relations and of regimes' choices. A structured comparative-historical argument highlights differing state strategies vis-a-vis important social forces, especially traditional chiefs. Regimes' choices between confrontation, coexistence, and the construction of new relations with social forces resulted in different degrees of local political change. The 'revolutionary' local experiments provide insight into a general theory of African politics, in which states' transformational powers in rural areas remain circumscribed by entrenched local forces. © ROAPE Publications Ltd., 2009.</ab>
<sn>03056244</sn>
<do>10.1080/03056240903346137</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>761</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Edgar,G. J.;Banks,S. A.;Brandt,M.;Bustamante,R. H.;Chiriboga,A.;Earle,S. A.;Garske,L. E.;Glynn,P. W.;Grove,J. S.;Henderson,S.;Hickman,C. P.;Miller,K. A.;Rivera,F.;Wellington,G. M.</a1>
<t1>El Niño, grazers and fisheries interact to greatly elevate extinction risk for Galapagos marine species</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Global Change Biology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>16</vo>
<is>10</is>
<sp>2876</sp>
<op>2890</op>
<ab>Comparisons between historical and recent ecological datasets indicate that shallow reef habitats across the central Galapagos Archipelago underwent major transformation at the time of the severe 1982/1983 El Niño warming event. Heavily grazed reefs with crustose coralline algae ('urchin barrens') replaced former macroalgal and coral habitats, resulting in large local and regional declines in biodiversity. Following recent threat assessment workshops, a total of five mammals, six birds, five reptiles, six fishes, one echinoderm, seven corals, six brown algae and nine red algae reported from coastal environments in Galapagos are now recognized as globally threatened. The 2008 International Union for the Conservation of Nature (IUCN) Red List includes 43 of these species, while two additional species (Galapagos damsel Azurina eupalama and 24-rayed sunstar Heliaster solaris) not seen for > 25 years also fulfil IU<cn>threatened species criteria. Two endemic species (Galapagos stringweed Bifurcaria galapagensis and the damselfish A. eupalama) are now regarded as probably extinct, while an additional six macroalgal species (Dictyota galapagensis, Spatoglossum schmittii, Desmarestia tropica, Phycodrina elegans, Gracilaria skottsbergii and Galaxaura barbata) and the seastar H. solaris are possibly extinct. The removal of large lobster and fish predators by artisanal fishing probably magnified impacts of the 1982/1983 El Niño through a cascade of indirect effects involving population expansion of grazing sea urchins. Marine protected areas with adequate enforcement are predicted to ameliorate but not eliminate ecosystem impacts caused by increasing thermal anomalies associated with El Niño and global climate change. © 2009 Blackwell Publishing Ltd.</ab></cn>
<sn>13541013</sn>
<do>10.1111/j.1365-2486.2009.02117.x</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>762</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Elmes,D. G.</a1>
<t1>Remembering and researching the old and the new: An interview with Roddy Roediger</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Teaching of Psychology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>37</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>216</sp>
<op>222</op>
<ab>Dr. Henry L. (Roddy) Roediger is the James S. McDonnell Distinguished University Professor in the Psychology Department at Washington University in St. Louis (WUSTL) and a scholar of human memory. He graduated from Washington & Lee University in 1969 and received his PhD in psychology from Yale University. He served as chair of the Psychology Department at WUSTL from 1996 to 2004, when he was named dean of academic planning in Arts and Sciences. Roediger's research interests include such topics as how people can suffer memory illusions and false memories (remembering events differently from the way they happened or remembering events that never happened at all)</a1>
<a1>implicit memory (when past events affect ongoing behavior without one's awareness)</a1>
<a1>and, most recently, applying cognitive psychology to improving learning in educational situations. One primary current interest is why the process of retrieval serves as a powerful memory enhancer. David G. Elmes is professor emeritus of psychology at Washington & Lee University, where he taught for 40 years. He earned undergraduate and graduate degrees from the University of Virginia. Elmes was a research associate at the Human Performance Center of the University of Michigan, and he was a Visiting Fellow of University College at the University of Oxford. He has coauthored or edited four books that focus on research methods and has numerous publications on learning, memory, and olfaction. Elmes served as president of the Council on Undergraduate Research. He is a fellow of the Association for Psychological Science and the Virginia Academy of Science. © Taylor & Francis Group, LLC.</ab>
<sn>00986283</sn>
<do>10.1080/00986283.2010.488536</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>763</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Erickson,J. C.;O'Grady,G.;Du,P.;Obioha,C.;Qiao,W.;Richards,W. O.;Bradshaw,L. A.;Pullan,A. J.;Cheng,L. K.</a1>
<t1>Falling-edge, variable threshold (FEVT) method for the automated detection of gastric slow wave events in high-resolution serosal electrode recordings</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Annals of Biomedical Engineering</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>38</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>1511</sp>
<op>1529</op>
<ab>High resolution (HR) multi-electrode mapping is increasingly being used to evaluate gastrointestinal slow wave behaviors. To create the HR activation time (AT) maps from gastric serosal electrode recordings that quantify slow wave propagation, it is first necessary to identify the AT of each individual slow wave event. Identifying these ATs has been a time consuming task, because there has previously been no reliable automated detection method. We have developed an automated AT detection method termed falling-edge, variable threshold (FEVT) detection. It computes a detection signal transform to accentuate the high 'energy' content of the falling edges in the serosal recording, and uses a running median estimator of the noise to set the time-varying detection threshold. The FEVT method was optimized, validated, and compared to other potential algorithms using in vivo HR recordings from a porcine model. FEVT properly detects ATs in a wide range of waveforms, making its performance substantially superior to the other methods, especially for low signal-to-noise ratio (SNR) recordings. The algorithm offered a substantial time savings (>100 times) over manual-marking whilst achieving a highly satisfactory sensitivity (0.92) and positive-prediction value (0.89). © 2009 Biomedical Engineering Society.</ab>
<sn>00906964</sn>
<do>10.1007/s10439-009-9870-3</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>764</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Evans,M. J.;Humke,P. D.</a1>
<t1>Two classes of Darboux-like, Baire one functions of two variables</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Czechoslovak Mathematical Journal</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>60</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>549</sp>
<op>569</op>
<ab>Among the many characterizations of the class of Baire one, Darboux realvalued functions of one real variable, the 1907 characterization of Young and the 1997 characterization of Agronsky, Ceder, and Pearson are particularly intriguing in that they yield interesting classes of functions when interpreted in the two-variable setting. We examine the relationship between these two subclasses of the real-valued Baire one defined on the unit square. © 2010 Mathematical Institute, Academy of Sciences of Czech Republic.</ab>
<sn>00114642</sn>
<do>10.1007/s10587-010-0036-0</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>765</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Evans,M. J.;Humke,P. D.</a1>
<t1>Revisiting a century-old characterization of baire class one, darboux functions</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>American Mathematical Monthly</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>116</vo>
<is>5</is>
<sp>451</sp>
<op>455</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>00029890</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>766</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Fafatas,S. A.</a1>
<t1>Auditor conservatism following audit failures</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Managerial Auditing Journal</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>25</vo>
<is>7</is>
<sp>639</sp>
<op>658</op>
<ab>Purpose: The purpose of this paper is to examine the effects of audit failure on Big 4 audit firm monitoring activities. The paper analyzes changes in discretionary accruals (DAs) among clients of firms implicated in audit failure events and examines whether these DAs decline in the period following the event. Design/methodology/approach: The paper uses archival data and regression analyses to test whether DAs for clients of implicated audit firms decline in the period following the audit failure as compared to clients of other Big 4 firms. Audit failures are identified during the years 1996-2004 based on significant lawsuit settlements. The paper focuses on an office-level analysis to control for audit quality differences which may vary across firm geographic locations as suggested by recent research. Findings: Empirical results indicate that auditor response to audit failure has changed over time. Auditors implicated in audit failure events occurring in the post-Enron and Sarbanes-Oxley period enforce more conservative accounting choices in the year following the event. Specifically, clients of the implicated firm's office report a significant decline in discretionary accounting accruals relative to clients of other auditors in the same city location. However, a significant change in client discretionary accounting accruals is not found following audit failures that occurred prior to 2001, the year of the Enron bankruptcy. Originality/value: The results of this paper extend the knowledge of the effects of litigation pressure on audit quality. Additionally, this paper helps address the question of how large-scale audit failures witnessed at the beginning of the century have impacted audit firm conservatism. © Emerald Group Publishing Limited.</ab>
<sn>02686902</sn>
<do>10.1108/02686901011061333</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>767</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Frye,G. D. J.;Lord,C. G.</a1>
<t1>Effects of time frame on the relationship between source monitoring errors and attitude change</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Social Cognition</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>27</vo>
<is>6</is>
<sp>867</sp>
<op>882</op>
<ab>One way to change attitudes is to induce people to act as though they already have the desired attitude. Another way is to induce people to imagine taking attitude-relevant actions. People who imagine taking an action sometimes forget whether they did it or only imagined it-a source monitoring error (SME). Previous research demonstrated a positive relationship between the number of attitude-relevant SMEs and attitude change (AC). The present experiments tested whether the imagined time frame might moderate this SME-AC relationship. The results indicated that the SME-AC relationship is equivalent for actions imagined in the past and future (Experiment 1), but occurs only for imagined attitude-relevant actions that occur in a near rather than distant imagined time frame (Experiment 2).</ab>
<sn>0278016X</sn>
<do>10.1521/soco.2009.27.6.867</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>768</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Fuentes,J. A.;France,M. B.;Slawin,A. M. Z.;Clarke,M. L.</a1>
<t1>Iridium complexes of chiral diamines containing carbon and nitrogen stereocentres: Synthesis, structure and evaluation as transfer hydrogenation catalysts</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>New Journal of Chemistry</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>33</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>466</sp>
<op>470</op>
<ab>Novel Rh(iii) and Ir(iii) complexes of a chiral diamine ligand have been synthesised and structurally characterised. Both complexes were formed as a single diastereomeric species with a single configuration at nitrogen. Ir complexes of the chiral diamine were found to be active in the asymmetric transfer hydrogenation of bulky ketones. Excellent conversions (up to 100%) and moderate enantioselectivities (up to 60%) were obtained in the asymmetric reduction of 2,2-dimethylpropiophenone. © The Royal Society of Chemistry and the Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique 2009.</ab>
<sn>11440546</sn>
<do>10.1039/b812699b</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>769</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Gagnon,G. J.;Nasr,N. M.;Liao,J. J.;Molzahn,I.;Marsh,D.;McRae,D.;Henderson,F. C.</a1>
<t1>Treatment of spinal tumors using cyberKnife fractionated stereotactic radiosurgery: Pain and quality-of-life assessment after treatment in 200 patients</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Neurosurgery</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>64</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>297</sp>
<op>306</op>
<ab>OBJECTIVE: Benign and malignant tumors of the spine significantly impair the function and quality of life of many patients. Standard treatment options, including conventional radiotherapy and surgery, are often limited by anatomic constraints and previous treatment. Image-guided stereotactic radiosurgery using the CyberKnife system (Accuray, Inc., Sunnyvale, CA) is a novel approach in the multidisciplinary management of spinal tumors. The aim of this study was to evaluate the effects of CyberKnife stereotactic radiosurgery on pain and quality-of-life outcomes of patients with spinal tumors. METHODS: We conducted a prospective study of 200 patients with benign or malignant spinal tumors treated at Georgetown University Hospital between March 2002 and September 2006. Patients were treated by means of multisession stereotactic radiosurgery using the CyberKnife as initial treatment, postoperative treatment, or retreatment. Pain scores were assessed by the Visual Analog Scale, quality of life was assessed by the SF-12 survey, and neurological examinations were conducted after treatment. RESULTS: Mean pain scores decreased significantly from 40.1 to 28.6 after treatment (P < 0.001) and continued to decrease over the entire 4-year follow-up period (P <0.05). SF-12 Physical Component scores demonstrated no significant change throughout the follow-up period. Mental Component scores were significantly higher after treatment (P < 0.01), representing a quality-of-life improvement. Early side effects of radiosurgery were mild and self-limited, and no late radiation toxicity was observed. CONCLUSION: CyberKnife stereotactic radiosurgery is a safe and effective modality in the treatment of patients with spinal tumors. CyberKnife offers durable pain relief and maintenance of quality of life with a very favorable side effect profile. Copyright © 2009 by the Congress of Neurological Surgeons.</ab>
<sn>0148396X</sn>
<do>10.1227/01.NEU.0000338072.30246.BD</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>770</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Ayoub,N. A.;Hayashi,C. Y.</a1>
<a1>Garb,J. E.;</a1>
<t1>Untangling spider silk evolution with spidroin terminal domains</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>BMC Evolutionary Biology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>10</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp></sp>
<op></op>
<ab>Background. Spidroins are a unique family of large, structural proteins that make up the bulk of spider silk fibers. Due to the highly variable nature of their repetitive sequences, spidroin evolutionary relationships have principally been determined from their non-repetitive carboxy (C)-terminal domains, though they offer limited character data. The few known spidroin amino (N)-terminal domains have been difficult to obtain, but potentially contain critical phylogenetic information for reconstructing the diversification of spider silks. Here we used silk gland expression data (ESTs) from highly divergent species to evaluate the functional significance and phylogenetic utility of spidroin N-terminal domains. Results. We report 11 additional spidroin N-termini found by sequencing ∼1,900 silk gland cDNAs from nine spider species that shared a common ancestor > 240 million years ago. In contrast to their hyper-variable repetitive regions, spidroin N-terminal domains have retained striking similarities in sequence identity, predicted secondary structure, and hydrophobicity. Through separate and combined phylogenetic analyses of N-terminal domains and their corresponding C-termini, we find that combined analysis produces the most resolved trees and that N-termini contribute more support and less conflict than the C-termini. These analyses show that paralogs largely group by silk gland type, except for the major ampullate spidroins. Moreover, spidroin structural motifs associated with superior tensile strength arose early in the history of this gene family, whereas a motif conferring greater extensibility convergently evolved in two distantly related paralogs. Conclusions. A non-repetitive N-terminal domain appears to be a universal attribute of spidroin proteins, likely retained from the origin of spider silk production. Since this time, spidroin N-termini have maintained several features, consistent with this domain playing a key role in silk assembly. Phylogenetic analyses of the conserved N- and C-terminal domains illustrate dramatic radiation of the spidroin gene family, involving extensive duplications, shifts in expression patterns and extreme diversification of repetitive structural sequences that endow spider silks with an unparalleled range of mechanical properties. © 2010 Garb et al</a1>
<a1>licensee BioMed Central Ltd.</ab>
<sn>14712148</sn>
<do>10.1186/1471-2148-10-243</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>771</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Gavrielides,A.;Sukow,D. W.;Burner,G.;McLachlan,T.;Miller,J.;Amonette,J.</a1>
<t1>Simple and complex square waves in an edge-emitting diode laser with polarization-rotated optical feedback</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Physical Review E - Statistical, Nonlinear, and Soft Matter Physics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>81</vo>
<is>5</is>
<sp> </sp>
<op> </op>
<ab>Numerical and experimental results are presented for an edge-emitting diode laser with delayed optical feedback, where the polarization state of the feedback is rotated such that the natural laser mode is coupled into the orthogonal, unsupported mode. We examine the bifurcation structure and dynamics that give rise to a class of periodic, polarization-modulated solutions, the simplest of which is a square wave solution with a period related to but longer than twice the external cavity roundtrip time. Such solutions typically emerge when the feedback is strong and the differential losses in the normally unsupported polarization mode are small. We also observe more complex waveforms that maintain the same periodicity. © 2010 The American Physical Society.</ab>
<sn>15393755</sn>
<do>10.1103/PhysRevE.81.056209</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>772</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Gerjouy,E.;Williams,H. Thomas;Bourdon,Paul S.</a1>
<t1>Augmented message-matrix approach to deterministic dense-coding theory</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Physical Review A - Atomic, Molecular, and Optical Physics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>79</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp></sp>
<op></op>
<ab>A useful method for deriving analytical results applicable to the standard two-party deterministic dense-coding protocol is introduced and illustrated. In this protocol, communication of K perfectly distinguishable messages is attainable via K selected local unitary operations performed on one qudit from a pair of entangled qudits of equal dimension d in a pure state |ψ with largest Schmidt coefficient λ0. The method takes advantage of the fact that the K message states, together with d2 -K augmenting orthonormal state vectors, yield a unitary matrix, thereby implying properties of the K message states which otherwise are not readily recognized. Employing this augmented message matrix, we produce simple proofs of previously established results including (i) λ0 ≤d/K, (ii) λ0 <d/K when K=d+1, and (iii) the impossibility of finding a |ψ that can enable transmission of K= d2 -1 messages but not d2. Additional results obtained using the method include proofs that the λ0 ≤d/K bound is reduced to at least (i) λ0 ≤ (1/2) [1+ (d-2) / (d+2)] when K=d+1 and (ii) λ0 ≤ (K-m) / (2K-m-d) whenever (d+1) ≤K≤2d and the selected local unitaries include the first m non-negative integral powers of the shift operator X. © 2009 The American Physical Society.</ab>
<sn>1050-2947</a1>
<a1>1094-1622</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>773</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Goldberg,N.</a1>
<t1>Response-dependence, noumenalism, and ontological mystery</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>European Journal of Philosophy</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>17</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>469</sp>
<op>488</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>09668373</sn>
<do>10.1111/j.1468-0378.2007.00280.x</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>774</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Goldberg,N.</a1>
<t1>Triangulation, untranslatability, and reconciliation</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Philosophia</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>37</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>261</sp>
<op>280</op>
<ab>Donald Davidson used triangulation to do everything from explicate psychological and semantic externalism, to attack relativism and skepticism, to propose conditions necessary for thought and talk. At one point Davidson tried to bring order to these remarks by identifying three kinds of triangulation, each operative in a different situation. Here I take seriously Davidson's talk of triangular situations and extend it. I start by describing Davidson's situations. Next I establish the surprising result that considerations from one situation entail the possibility that at any one time one language is partially untranslatable into another. Because the possibility is time-indexed, it need not conflict with Davidson's own argument against the possibility of untranslatability. I derive the result, not to indict Davidson, but to propose a new kind of triangulation, the reconciliation of untranslatability, which I investigate. Insofar as triangulation is central to Davidson's views, getting a handle on his various triangular situations is key to getting a handle on his contributions to philosophy. Insofar as those contributions have enriched our understanding of how language, thought, and reality interrelate, extending Davidson's model promises to extend our understanding too. © 2008 Springer Science+Business Media B.V.</ab>
<sn>00483893</sn>
<do>10.1007/s11406-008-9171-3</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>775</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Goldberg,N. J.</a1>
<t1>Historicism, entrenchment, and conventionalism</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Journal for General Philosophy of Science</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>40</vo>
<is>2</is>
<sp>259</sp>
<op>276</op>
<ab>W. V. Quine famously argues that though all knowledge is empirical, mathematics is entrenched relative to physics and the special sciences. Further, entrenchment accounts for the necessity of mathematics relative to these other disciplines. Michael Friedman challenges Quine's view by appealing to historicism, the thesis that the nature of science is illuminated by taking into account its historical development. Friedman argues on historicist grounds that mathematical claims serve as principles constitutive of languages within which empirical claims in physics and the special sciences can be formulated and tested, where these mathematical claims are themselves not empirical but conventional. For Friedman, their conventional, constitutive status accounts for the necessity of mathematics relative to these other disciplines. Here I evaluate Friedman's challenge to Quine and Quine's likely response. I then show that though we have reason to find Friedman's challenge successful, his positive project requires further development before we can endorse it. © 2009 Springer Science+Business Media B.V.</ab>
<sn>09254560</sn>
<do>10.1007/s10838-009-9097-x</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>778</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Grajzl,P.;Dimitrova-Grajzl,V.</a1>
<t1>The choice in the lawmaking process: Legal transplants vs. Indigenous law</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Review of Law and Economics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>5</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp> </sp>
<op> </op>
<ab>We develop a model of lawmaking to study the efficiency implications of, and variation in, jurisdictions' choices between promulgation of indigenously developed laws and legal transplants. Our framework emphasizes the sequential nature of lawmaking, the ubiquity of uncertainty, considerations about ex-ante promulgation versus ex-post adjustment costs, and the importance of the political context of legal reform. In discerning the patterns of inefficiencies in both transplantation and indigenous lawmaking, we elucidate the role of heterogeneity of interests and adaptability of a legal system. We also find that domestic corruption per se need not justify transplantation of foreign legal models. Our results support the view that local conditions are a crucial determinant of the appropriate path of institutional reform. © 2009 by bepress.</ab>
<sn>15555879</sn>
<do>10.2202/1555-5879.1402</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>779</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Greer,L.;Jackson,J. E.;Curran,H. A.;Guilderson,T.;Teneva,L.</a1>
<t1>How vulnerable is Acropora cervicornis to environmental change? Lessons from the early to middle Holocene</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Geology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>37</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>263</sp>
<op>266</op>
<ab>The coral Acropora cervicornis is considered a modern environmental indicator species, vulnerable to anthropogenic stress and rapidly disappearing throughout the Caribbean. Causes for its decline have been attributed to both natural and anthropogenic factors. Physical and geochemical data are used to explore conditions under which this species thrived in early to middle Holocene reef deposits (ca. 9.4-5.4 ka) of the Enriquillo Valley, southwestern Dominican Republic. This study shows that A. cervicornis flourished during a 4000 yr period spanning the Holocene Thermal Maximum, and high-resolution radiocarbon dating reveals continuous growth for at least 2000 yr. Holocene A. cervicornis survived large-scale climate and environmental changes that included high temperatures, variable salinity, hurricanes, and rapid sea-level rise with remarkable resilience. Our data suggest that the recent decline in A. cervicornis is anomalous and likely tied to ecosystem change beyond natural causes. © 2009 The Geological Society of America.</ab>
<sn>00917613</sn>
<do>10.1130/G25479A.1</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>780</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Grizzard,Frank E.</a1>
<t1>143 questions & answers about George Washington</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>136</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780982017258</a1>
<a1>0982017251</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4>b1722752</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>781</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Hamilton,D.;Goldsmith,A. H.;Darity Jr.,W.</a1>
<t1>Shedding light on marriage: The influence of skin shade on marriage for black females</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Journal of Economic Behavior and Organization</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>72</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp>30</sp>
<op>50</op>
<ab>The inter-racial marriage gap that opened in the past 50 years is generally attributed to a decline in the availability of young black marriageable men. We contend that the associated shortage of desirable men in the marriage market provides those black men who are sought after with the opportunity to attain a high status spouse, which has placed a premium on black women with lighter skin. We provide evidence, based on data drawn from the Multi City Study of Urban Inequality, consistent with this hypothesis. Our theoretical analysis of the marriage market reveals that marriage promotion policies to increase the desire to marry on the part of young black women will serve to exacerbate the importance attached to skin shade. © 2009 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</ab>
<sn>01672681</sn>
<do>10.1016/j.jebo.2009.05.024</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>782</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Holyk,G. G.</a1>
<t1>The polls - Trends: U.s. public support for the united nations</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Public opinion quarterly</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>74</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp>168</sp>
<op>189</op>
<ab>In the aftermath of the failure to come to a diplomatic resolution regarding Iraq in 2003 and the subsequent military strike by the United States and its allies without United Nations (UN) approval, the usefulness and role of international diplomatic institutions such as the UN are undergoing a reexamination. The U.S. public has shown a high degree of general support for the UN since its inception. Although judgments of UN performance rose and fell over the years, support for strengthening the UN and for continued U.S. participation and cooperation with the UN remained strong and stable. Most notably, approval of UN performance dropped to an all-time low between 2003 and 2007, after the contentious debate over the use of force against Iraq. Nonetheless, support for the UN has remained strong because the U.S. public differentiates between criticism of UN performance and support for the general purpose and aims of the UN.</ab>
<sn>0033362X</sn>
<do>10.1093/poq/nfp088</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>783</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Jasiewicz,K.</a1>
<t1>The past is never dead: Identity, class, and voting behavior in contemporary poland</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>East European Politics and Societies</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>23</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>491</sp>
<op>508</op>
<ab>This article presents a summary of analyses addressing the changing patterns of voting behavior in post-communist Poland as a context for examination of the issue of the relationship between regions defined by history (eighteenth-century partitions, border shifts after WWII) and contemporary forms of voting behavior. In the 1990s, the dominant cleavage in Polish politics was the one between the post-Solidarity and post-communist camps, and the best predictor of voting behavior was one's religiosity. In the first decade of the twenty-first century, this cleavage has been replaced by another, between the liberal, pro-European orientation and the more Euro-skeptic, populist attitudes. The empirical evidence seems to suggest that one end of the populist-liberal continuum is relatively well defined and represents the traditional system of values, which defines Polish national identity in terms of ethnic nationalism, strong attachment to Catholic dogmas, and denunciation of communism as a virtual negation of those values. The other end of this continuum is defined more by rejection of this nationalistic-Catholic imagined community than by any positive features. This article examines the relative role of identity-related factors (e.g., religiosity or region) and determinants based on one's socioeconomic (class) position in shaping voting patterns in the 2007 elections to the Polish Sejm and Senate. The empirical data come from a postelection survey, the Polish General Election Study 2007. © 2009 Sage Publications.</ab>
<sn>08883254</sn>
<do>10.1177/0888325409342114</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>784</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Jasiewicz,K.;Jasiewicz-Betkiewicz,A.</a1>
<t1>Poland</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>European Journal of Political Research</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>48</vo>
<is>8-Jul</is>
<sp>1073</sp>
<op>1079</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>03044130</sn>
<do>10.1111/j.1475-6765.2009.01883.x</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>785</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Jeans,Roger B.</a1>
<t1>Terasaki Hidenari, Pearl Harbor, and occupied Japan :a bridge to reality</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf> </jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo> </vo>
<is> </is>
<sp>277</sp>
<op> </op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780739134009</a1>
<a1>0739134000</a1>
<a1>9780739134023</a1>
<a1>0739134027</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>DS885.5.T4J436 2009</cn>
<u4>b1718892</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>786</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Johnson,D. R.</a1>
<t1>Emotional Attention Set-Shifting and Its Relationship to Anxiety and Emotion Regulation</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Emotion</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>9</vo>
<is>5</is>
<sp>681</sp>
<op>690</op>
<ab>Attentional deployment is a primary strategy individuals use to regulate emotion. In 2 experiments, a measure of an individual's ability to deploy attention toward and away from emotional mental representations was developed. This measure of attentional control capacity for emotion adapted an explicit-cuing task switching paradigm in which participants had to shift between emotional and neutral mental sets. Experiment 1 (N = 118) showed that those higher in trait anxiety and worrisome thoughts took longer to switch from a neutral to an emotional mental set. In Experiment 2 (N = 42), participants were given a stressful anagram task, and those who switched more efficiently from a neutral set to an emotional set were more frustrated by the stressful task. In addition, those who switched more efficiently from an emotional set to a neutral set persisted longer on the stressful task. These findings provide an initial step toward identifying possible mechanisms through which individuals apply attentional control to emotional mental representations to regulate emotion. © 2009 American Psychological Association.</ab>
<sn>15283542</sn>
<do>10.1037/a0017095</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>787</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Johnson,Lyman P.;Garvis,Dennis M.</a1>
<t1>Are corporate officers advised about fiduciary duties?</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Business Lawyer</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>64</vo>
<is>4</is>
<sp>1105</sp>
<op>1128</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>0007-6899</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>788</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Kuehner,J. P.;Tessier Jr.,F. A.;Kisoma,A.;Flittner,J. G.;McErlean,M. R.</a1>
<t1>Measurements of mean and fluctuating temperature in an underexpanded jet using electrostrictive laser-induced gratings</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Experiments in Fluids</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>48</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>421</sp>
<op>430</op>
<ab>Instantaneous temperature measurements were obtained in an underexpanded jet using electrostrictive laser-induced gratings. Evaluation of the technique under static, low-pressure conditions provided a baseline uncertainty or precision for single-shot temperature measurements of 4.4% of the local mean temperature, which represents the minimum detectable temperature fluctuation. The underexpanded jet was operated at a nozzle pressure ratio of 2.39 and a fully expanded jet Mach number of 1.19. Data were acquired along the centerline and over two radial traverses through the shear layer. Mean temperature data agree well with expectations, describing the shock-cell structure and the compressible shear layer. The growth in shear-layer width with downstream distance can be identified in the mean and fluctuating temperature measurements. Temperature fluctuations are near the baseline detection limit in the jet core and surrounding ambient air, and reach a maximum in the shear layer. The temperature fluctuation measurements compare well with previous computational and experimental work, confirming the application of the technique to a turbulent, supersonic flow. © 2009 Springer-Verlag.</ab>
<sn>07234864</sn>
<do>10.1007/s00348-009-0746-y</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>789</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Lambert,Kenneth</a1>
<a1>Osborne,Martin</a1>
<t1>Fundamentals of Python: from first programs through data structures</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>915</sp>
<op></op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9781423902188</a1>
<a1>1423902181</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>QA76.73.P98L36 2010</cn>
<u4>b1723772</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>790</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>LaRiviere,F. J.;Newman,A. G.;Watts,M. L.;Bradley,S. Q.;Juskewitch,J. E.;Greenwood,P. G.;Millard,J. T.</a1>
<t1>Quantitative PCR analysis of diepoxybutane and epihalohydrin damage to nuclear versus mitochondrial DNA</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Mutation Research - Fundamental and Molecular Mechanisms of Mutagenesis</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>664</vo>
<is>2-Jan</is>
<sp>48</sp>
<op>54</op>
<ab>The bifunctional alkylating agents diepoxybutane (DEB) and epichlorohydrin (ECH) are linked to the elevated incidence of certain cancers among workers in the synthetic polymer industry. Both compounds form interstrand cross-links within duplex DNA, an activity suggested to contribute to their cytotoxicity. To assess the DNA targeting of these compounds in vivo, we assayed for damage within chicken erythro-progenitor cells at three different sites: one within mitochondrial DNA, one within expressed nuclear DNA, and one within unexpressed nuclear DNA. We determined the degree of damage at each site via a quantitative polymerase chain reaction, which compares amplification of control, untreated DNA to that from cells exposed to the agent in question. We found that ECH and the related compound epibromohydrin preferentially target nuclear DNA relative to mitochondrial DNA, whereas DEB reacts similarly with the two genomes. Decreased reactivity of the mitochondrial genome could contribute to the reduced apoptotic potential of ECH relative to DEB. Additionally, formation of lesions by all agents occurred at comparable levels for unexpressed and expressed nuclear loci, suggesting that alkylation is unaffected by the degree of chromatin condensation. © 2009 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</ab>
<sn>00275107</sn>
<do>10.1016/j.mrfmmm.2009.02.004</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>791</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Larkin,M. F.;Ault,J. S.;Humston,R.;Luo,J.</a1>
<t1>A mail survey to estimate the fishery dynamics of southern Florida's bonefish charter fleet</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf>Fisheries Management and Ecology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>17</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>254</sp>
<op>261</op>
<ab>Bonefish, Albula vulpes (L.), support an economically important recreational fishery in southern Florida, USA that has received little scientific study and has never been adequately assessed. A mail survey of 322 captains that comprise the southern Florida bonefish charter fleet was conducted to acquire a baseline understanding of the primary fishery statistics. The response rate was 59% and a follow-up telephone survey of non-respondents indicated no non-response bias. Experience in the fishery ranged from 3 to 61 years. The annual fishing effort was 30 875 boat days. The majority of the fleet fishing effort occurred in the northern Florida Keys and is presumed to reflect bonefish abundance. The instantaneous mortality rate of released fish was 0.11 year-1. The majority of the respondents indicated that the bonefish stock had declined over the past decade. © 2010 Blackwell Publishing Ltd.</ab>
<sn>0969997X</sn>
<do>10.1111/j.1365-2400.2009.00718.x</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>792</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>LeBlanc,Robin M.</a1>
<t1>The art of the gut: manhood, power, and ethics in Japanese politics</t1>
<yr>2010</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>229</sp>
<op></op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780520259164</a1>
<a1>0520259165</a1>
<a1>9780520259171</a1>
<a1>0520259173</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole</rt>
<u3>Book, Whole</u3>
<cn>HQ1090.5.J3L4 2010</cn>
<u4>b1729754</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>793</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Lorig,T. S.</a1>
<t1>What was the question? fMRI and inference in psychophysiology</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>International Journal of Psychophysiology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>73</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp>17</sp>
<op>21</op>
<ab>fMRI research has spent its first generation determining areas of high activation in the brain during various psychological tasks. The technique has proved exceedingly useful for asking where is the brain active during these tasks. This paper investigates the utility of asking the question where is the brain active and provides the reader with a useful analogy to simplify the logic and decisions being made when doing fMRI research. Rationales are considered for asking both the questions: where is the brain active and how does the brain work?. © 2008 Elsevier B.V. All rights reserved.</ab>
<sn>01678760</sn>
<do>10.1016/j.ijpsycho.2009.01.004</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>794</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Marco,A. C.</a1>
<t1>The economics of a centralized judiciary: Uniformity, forum shopping, and the Federal Circuit</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Journal of Law and Economics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>52</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>411</sp>
<op>443</op>
<ab>In 1982, the U.S. Congress established the Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit (CAFC) as the sole appellate court for patent cases. This court was created ostensibly to eliminate inconsistencies in the application and interpretation of patent law across federal courts and thereby mitigate the incentives of patentees and alleged infringers to forum shop for a preferred venue. We perform the first econometric study of the extent of nonuniformity and forum shopping in the pre-CAFC era and of the CAFC's impact on these phenomena. We find that in patentee-plaintiff cases the pre-CAFC era was indeed characterized by significant nonuniformity in patent validity rates across circuits and by forum shopping on the basis of validity rates. We find weak evidence that the CAFC has increased uniformity of validity rates and strong evidence that forum shopping on the basis of validity rates ceased several years prior to the CAFC's establishment. © 2009 by The University of Chicago. All rights reserved.</ab>
<sn>0022-2186</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>795</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Marco,A. C.;Van Woerden,A. S.;Woodward,R. M.</a1>
<t1>The problem of shared social cost</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Review of Law and Economics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>5</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp> </sp>
<op> </op>
<ab>This paper presents a mechanism for regulating pollution when industry harm - but not individual firms' contributions - is observable. The mechanism is based on a modification of Cooter and Porat's Total Liability for Excessive Harm (TLEH). We propose an alternative mechanism of Shared Social Costs (SSC), where firms share the total cost of industry harm and abatement costs. In cases where the abatement costs for each firm are verifiable, SSC may provide an efficient alternative to TLEH. The mechanisms are largely equivalent, but require different types of information for the regulator. For a legal target to be set in TLEH, it requires either knowing the cost functions of individual firms or accommodating error costs by gradually reducing the legal target until the efficient level is found. On the other hand, SSC requires observing individual firms' actual abatement expenditures as opposed to knowing their cost functions. Both rules provide efficient incentives for abatement, and require being able to observe and monetize industry level harm. We show that SSC leads to efficient incentives for entry and exit, has appealing incentives for innovation, and can be applied advantageously to remediation. In markets with heterogeneous firms, we propose weighting cost-sharing by firms' market shares. © 2009 by bepress.</ab>
<sn>15555879</sn>
<do>10.2202/1555-5879.1252</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>796</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Marsh,D.</a1>
<t1>Evaluating methods for sampling stream Salamanders across multiple observers and habitat types</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Applied Herpetology</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>6</vo>
<is>3</is>
<sp>211</sp>
<op>226</op>
<ab>While techniques for sampling pond-breeding amphibians are relatively well-established, comparable methods for stream amphibians are still being developed. Uncertainty about sampling techniques is particularly acute for approaches that involve multiple observers. I evaluated three techniques for sampling stream salamanders with multiple observers-time-constrained surveys, leaf-litter bags, and controlled-cobble added to the stream. I tested for differences among techniques, differences among habitats, and technique by habitat interactions. I also asked whether coefficients of variation across observers and sample dates differed among methods and habitats. For all species and life-stages, time-constrained surveys produced higher counts of stream salamanders and greater richness estimates than did leaf-litter bags or controlled-cobble surveys. However, interactions between techniques and habitat were never significant, indicating that all the methods detected similar patterns in counts among stream habitats. Coefficients of variation in single-species counts tended to be higher for time-constrained surveys, whereas CVs for species richness were significantly lower for time-constrained surveys. Overall, these results suggest that: (1) time-constrained surveys for stream salamanders work surprisingly well even with multiple observers, (2) leaf-litter bags may be quite useful for single-species studies, but are less effective for multi-species sampling, and (3) controlled-cobble added to streams is not particularly effective for sampling salamanders in rocky streams. © 2009 Koninklijke Brill NV, Leiden.</ab>
<sn>15707539</sn>
<do>10.1163/157075408X386178</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>797</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Mahon,James Edwin</a1>
<t1>The truth about Kant on lies</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf></jf>
<t2>The philosophy of deception</t2>
<vo></vo>
<is></is>
<sp>201</sp>
<op>224</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>9780195327939</a1>
<a1>0195327934</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Book, Whole, Chapter/Section</rt>
<u3>Book, Section</u3>
<cn>BJ1421.P45 2009</cn>
<u4>b1733774</u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>798</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Mayock,E.</a1>
<t1>Nostalgia for itself in my real life I know nothing of Ana María Moix</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Anales de la Literatura Espanola Contemporanea</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>34</vo>
<is>1</is>
<sp>137</sp>
<op>157</op>
<ab> </ab>
<sn>02721635</sn>
<do> </do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>799</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Mazilu,I.;Williams,H. T.</a1>
<t1>Exact energy spectrum of a two-temperature kinetic Ising model</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>Physical Review E - Statistical, Nonlinear, and Soft Matter Physics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>80</vo>
<is>6</is>
<sp></sp>
<op></op>
<ab>We develop the exact energy spectrum for a two-temperature kinetic Ising spin chain and its dual reaction-diffusion system with spatially alternating pair annihilation and creation rates. We also discuss the symmetries of the system pseudo-Hamiltonian and their role in developing a general solution. The surprisingly simple form for the eigenvalues leads to interesting physical consequences and to a possible numerical analysis of the dynamical properties of the system. © 2009 The American Physical Society.</ab>
<sn>15393755</sn>
<do>10.1103/PhysRevE.80.061109</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn></cn>
<u4></u4>
</reference>
<reference>
<id>800</id>
<u1>0</u1>
<a1>Mazilu,I.;Williams,H. T.</a1>
<t1>Nonequilibrium statistical mechanics: A solvable model</t1>
<yr>2009</yr>
<jf>American Journal of Physics</jf>
<t2></t2>
<vo>77</vo>
<is>5</is>
<sp>458</sp>
<op>467</op>
<ab>A two-temperature linear spin model is presented as an introduction to nonequilibrium statistical physics. The model involves the concepts that are typical of more realistic nonequilibrium models, but has straightforward steady state solutions and, for small systems, development of the full time dependence for configuration probabilities. The model is accessible to upper-level undergraduates and provides a good check of computer models for larger systems. © 2009 American Association of Physics Teachers.</ab>
<sn>00029505</sn>
<do>10.1119/1.3081423</do>
<rt>Journal Article</rt>
<u3>Journal Article</u3>
<cn> </cn>
<u4> </u4>
</reference>

</refworks>